So friends, today we are going to talk to you
about Gift Select Plan of ICICI Preferential Life Insurance and
obviously friends, this is such a plan in which
you
can enjoy life insurance as well as SWP.
Now what is SWP?  Friends, you know
that there
is a concept in the mutual fund industry called SWP i.e.
Systematic Withdrawal Plan.  That is,
like we do SIP.  For example,
a fixed amount is deducted from you on a particular date
and then it gets invested
in mutual funds.  Similarly, if you do SWP, that is,
you deposit money all at once and
then you start getting monthly income, that is
called SWP i.e. Systematic Withdrawal Plan.  If I talk about the same principle, it can be
seen in life insurance also.  Friends, if I
talk about this plan, then I like this
plan very much.  So if you want a quotation for yourself and
want to purchase this plan, you will
get the number in the description.
You can contact him on this, you
can WhatsApp him.  You will be fully helped by
ICICI Prudential and obviously
friends, we will fully help you in purchasing this plan and will
also tell you all the other things in detail.  So now let us know what this
plan is like.  Friends, the name of this plan
is ICIC PDL Gift Select Plan.  So
friends, let us now understand
this plan in detail and obviously
how will I explain the plan to you.  I will
not show the brochure directly.  I will
show you this plan by making a quotation that
if there is a person who is trying to purchase that plan then
what benefits he is going to get.  So
I have obviously made a quotation in this plan.
So we will definitely move on the screen.
Before this, let me tell you what edge zooms I have done in the plan.
I assume
that there is a 32 year old man.
Why have I kept it for 32 years now?  Because generally
if you look at India, if someone gets married at the age of 26, 27, 28
i.e. 30 years
and then has a child in the next one or two years.  Then again
he thinks about all these things.
However, life insurance
is very important.  First of all get your health insurance done.
Then get life insurance
and after that friends, you should
look at other investment options.  So,
I have assumed here that there is a 32
year old person who is
interested in buying this plan.  So
friends, according to that, we have brought the quotations here.
Now, as you are moving on the screen,
you can see all these
things on the side.  Now you can also see some options
in this like features like
life insurance cover.  This means that
you understand the meaning of life insurance cover that
if suppose you buy this plan
and God forbid something goes
wrong with you, then the
life insurance i.e. a fixed amount as per the
sum insured that you have taken will be
given to your nominee.
You will also get to see flexible options in this.
As I have talked about income here, it is
not that you have to
wait continuously till the end.
As soon as you implement this plan, you
can start getting a monthly income or
you can also take it yearly.  So you will get
to see flexible options.  The
option of guaranteed regular income,
as I have already told you, is already there
and you can also see the loan against policy.
However, friends,
if I talk about this, then generally you get
to see a loan on insurance policy.
If you have taken any other policy, then you
can take a loan on that basis also,
but here it has been said that the
interest rate will be that if you
take a loan amount on the basis of the policy,
whatever is allotted to you, then the
interest rate on that will be very nominal.  So we will
see that.  After that, if
we talk about Snaps, then obviously
you get it in the plan.  So as
I already told you, he is a 32 year old man.  He is a
man, which means he is a male.  So if we
talk about this, now look at it,
if you take this plan for granted, then
you can deposit the premium for 10 years.
Take it for 10 years, that is,
your premium paying term should be 10 years and then
you should be provided income for 20 years.
Now the income is not something that will be available after 10 years.
That will happen from the first year.  I will
explain that to you.  So in this we assume
that your annual
premium for the year is coming.  Now you
can deposit it monthly, quarterly
, half yearly or even
yearly if someone pays it, then
I will assume that if someone is paying ₹1 lakh premium
yearly also.  Now you know that
taxes like GST etc. have been abolished, so
your premium of ₹1 lakh will be charged only as ₹1 lakh.
So if someone selects a premium of ₹1 lakh,
he pays ₹1 lakh in a year.
If you have to pay monthly, then
divide Rs 1 lakh by 12 and whatever
your installment will be, you can deposit it monthly
there also.  So here we
can see that if
someone takes this policy in December 2025 and
deposits ₹1 lakh every year for the next 10 years.
So generally you must have seen in insurance
that one thing is that first the money has to be
deposited.  Then after some time,
after 10 years or extra, you will
get some returns.  But this is not the case.
In this, suppose today is 26th December
when I am making this video.  So
suppose you purchased this plan on 26th December.
Obviously, within two-three days your
policy will be completely written and
you will get the policy.  So, after two-three days,
as soon as the policy is finalised, within
seven days, you will get a cashback of Rs 30,000 i.e. 30% of the
premium you deposited.
Cashback means that if
you paid a premium of Rs 1 lakh, suppose on 26th December in the first year, then
you should have approximately
4-5 working days before 4th January,
within that
you will get ₹00 back.  So
how much premium did you lose?  70,000, so now the
overall thing is that as soon as you
deposited the premium of 1 lakh, you got some of it, so you collected it and got a
cashback of ₹00, which
you can see that as soon as I took the policy in December 2025,
in this you got instant cashback
of ₹0000 on policy issue, as soon as the policy was issued,
you got ₹00.  It's a simple matter.
Now in December 2025, you deposited ₹1300 and
you got it.  When will you deposit it now?
In December 2026.  Now when you submit it in December 2026, there is
an option in which
your income will be counted from the second year.  It will be
considered from the second year.  Meaning there should be a
gap of one year.  So, just like we
deposited ₹1 lakh in December 2025, we got ₹00 cashback.
Now when you deposit
₹1 lakh in December 2026, you will not get anything at that time.  You won't
get anything that year.
But after that when will your next premium
come?  In December 2027, from December 2027 to
December 2034, because we are talking about the next 10
years, then from December 2025
to 2034, there is a time of 10 years, so you will
not get anything in 2026, but from 2027, as soon as
you deposit ₹1 lakh,
you will start getting a fixed yearly income of approximately ₹32200.  If
you want, you can take it monthly
, quarterly or even half
yearly.  That again is in your hands.
So in December 2027, when you deposit Rs 1 lakh,
you will get Rs 32,200 there again.
And similarly, till
when will you keep getting these ₹32,200?  Sorry, the
20 years that I mentioned in political policy
terms are not 20 years.  I have been here for
25 years, taking political policy terms.
So now you have to deposit the premium for 10 years
and after that
you will keep getting ₹32,200 every year till December 2050.  So there is an
advantage in terms of how much premium you spent.
Well, if you are depositing ₹1
lakh every year for 10 years, then
your premium should be ₹10 lakh.
But you got ₹00 back in the very first year
and after that, except for one year, then next
year if you have written 8 more years when you will be
depositing the premium, then you will get ₹32,200
back every year and it is
not that after getting this ₹32,200, when
it will be completed by 2050, by December 2050,
then whatever you had deposited in December 2050, that is, you will
also get the maturity amount of ₹1 lakh which you had deposited in December 2050,
that is, 10 lakh more out of 10 lakh will be returned in December 2050.
So this is such a plan and
along with it risk cover is also included that
if God forbid some mishap happens in between then
you are depositing ₹1 lakh for a
year, if mishap happens at any time then
you will get 10 times cover of ₹1
lakh, that is simple thing, it will be given to the nominee,
now it may be due to any reason, whether
normal or accidental, it does not matter, then
₹1 lakh will be given to the nominee there
and if nothing happens to you at all and
God blesses you, then after getting ₹
32200 every year in 2050,
you will get ₹1 lakh more on maturity in December 2050.
As you
can see here, in the benefit details also,
you can see that the life insurance cover will be for
10 years and for 25 years i.e.
till December 2050.  So the overall thing is
that if you look at some of the features,
you are getting instant cashback of ₹0000.
Generally people accept and expect
that they should get something, when I have taken a
policy, they want that
I want something from the very first day, so you will get instant cashback of ₹00
on the policy issue, then you have a guaranteed income of ₹32200
which you will get for the next 24 years,
remember if you take a policy this year, then after one year
when you pay the premium you will not get anything at that time,
we are talking from the next year onwards, so
you will keep getting ₹32200 yearly for 24 years, that is from December 2027, you will keep getting
this 32,200 for the next 24 years i.e. till 2050,
and after that obviously the
total premium you deposited in December 2050 was only 10 lakh, by adding 1 lakh and the
10 lakh deposited for 10 years, that too will be
returned to you in December 2050.
So now if I talk about its benefits, what
benefit did I get by doing this plan, then
you can see that the total
benefit, if we add instant cashback
, guaranteed income,
maturity benefit, then it becomes
₹18,2800.  That means
we deposited ₹1 lakh.  Now this
is beneficial why?  You may ask me
where is this like a mutual fund
where I am getting regular income?  So
I will answer that.  Firstly, life
insurance obviously
protects your family.  If God
forbid something happens, if the nominee gets something, then
that cover is always with them.
If you want to increase it further, then
instead of Rs 1 lakh, if you deposit Rs 5 lakh in a year,
then it will cover Rs 50 lakh.
So that is your capacity as to how much you
want to increase it.  So risk cover is definitely
included.  Along with this, when you
deposit the premium every year, sometimes a
person gets the insurance done but
after that he starts feeling a headache that friend, I have a
separate expense for
2030 and I have to pay this installment also,
then he gets a headache.  So what happens in this case is that if
you deposit the premium then
you will also get some returns along with it.  For example, if
you look at Rs 32,200 in a year,
you are depositing Rs 1 lakh.  32,200 is coming back to you.
So approximately, you are getting back around 32%
every year.
And after that, whatever you have deposited, you will obviously keep getting it for the
next 25 years for 32 years
and the Rs 10 lakh that you had deposited,
that too will be returned to you when the policy ends, that
means Rs 10 lakh for Rs 10 lakh,
so if you see the returns, it is very good.  There is
also risk cover in this, so the returns are coming out to be very
good.  Risk cover
is included.  That means it is
an excellent package for life insurance.  If you
compare this plan with other policies, you will find it
quite appropriate.  If you are interested in this, then you will
find the number in the description,
please contact on that.  Our team will
help you completely in purchasing this plan
and obviously will ensure that you do
not face any problem.  Absolutely all your
questions will be answered.  So
friends, this plan is very good.
You can also look for additional flexibility.
What is there in it?  Loan on Policy,
as I already told you, you can always have
their app, once this policy is done, then there is an
app of ICICI.  You will see this policy on it.   If you
want, you can also take a loan
on your policy there.  You can also postpone your
income.  Now see
what is the benefit of flexibility flexibility to postpone income?  Let me
tell you.  For example, suppose you have
deposited the premium.  There are many people who
may not need income at that time.  That
means
if I feel that I don't need the money of Rs 32,200 that is coming, right now.
I will take it after some time, so you
can pause it.  And what will be the benefit of pausing it that
your fixed income will increase in the coming time.  It will not happen that there will be
any loss in it.  It will definitely be beneficial
because you will also get interest on it, which can be
very less or very high.
That way you will see.
However, all this is a matter of time, when you do it,
you will know the exact value only when
you have taken the policy, so
if you see the premium paid every year for 10 years, it is going to be
₹1 lakh and you are going to get a
benefit of about ₹182800 and
as you have seen here that
after the abolition of GST, your yearly premium will be
₹1 lakh, there are no taxes, it has become
zero, brother, so the total yearly
premium will also remain ₹1 lakh, earlier things
were different, 45% in the first year, then 2.25%
in the second year, so all those things are over.
Why should you choose ICICI PSU now?
No need to tell brother.  Nowadays, if
you look at it, everything is very simple.  You
can get insurance plans from anywhere.
Whether you take it from LIC, HDFC or
ICIC, everything is equal
because IRDA is controlling everything.   That
means, if your claim etc.
is absolutely genuine then there will never be any problem
and our team will also
help you.  So, to purchase this plan, do
contact us and
you can get your quotation made from us according to your age.
We will help you completely.  The
ICICI team will also
help you completely.  So if you
like the video then please like it.  If you have any doubt, please
write it in the comment.  I will
try to clear it up.
Rest you can connect with us on WhatsApp.
So thank you so much friends.
Happy New Year in advance to everyone.